relive.cc 2018-10-03

# Relive

Relive B.V. protects your personal data and privacy. In this privacy policy, we tell you which personal data we collect and in what way we store and use it. This privacy policy applies to our website [www.relive.cc](https://www.relive.cc/) (the Website), our application listed in the Apple Store and Google Play Store (the Application) and the services we provide. If you are under 16 years of age you need prior permission of your parents or legal guardians to use the website or Application.

### Why we process personal data

#### To provide our service

In order to start using Relive, you need to sign up and create an account. In this step you provide us with information such as your name, email address and a profile picture (optional). We use this personal data (account data) so that you can log in to Relive, to personalize the service and so that we know how to address you when we contact you.

When you connect a third party provider, like Strava or Garmin, you allow us to retrieve and store information from their service on your behalf including your profile information on the third party service in order to fill and update your Relive profile. You also allow us to process activity data from those third parties.

We process your activity data such as your tracked route, photos you upload and other information you add to the activity to create your Personal Video or for instance a personal heatmap. You can allow us to share activity data with other users to for instance create group videos (Relive Together).

We may also use anonymized aggregated data to create additional features within our service. For instance, aggregated activity data can be used to generate route recommendations or to create a heatmap. We may also use, sell, license, and share this anonymized information with third parties for research, business or other purposes.

Note that when you use Relive via a third party tracker the activity data can include your heart rate, we are not able to delete this info as it is often embedded in the received activity data.

You can upgrade your personal account and use a premium service of Relive (Relive Club). To bring you Relive Club we process required payment information.

#### To improve and protect our service

We process data on how you use our service such as the features you use, the actions you take and the time, frequency and duration of your usage. We also store non-personal data, such as: the type of your browser, the type of your computer and technical information on how you are reaching our website or app. This helps us to improve our service and to quickly detect crashes and bugs so that we can fix them.

#### To contact you

We use your information to communicate with you about our service (e.g.: when you’ve forgotten your password or when your video is ready), to help you use our service and to update you about our service and share other information we think you like. We also use your information to respond to you when you contact us. You can manage your contact settings on your profile.

### Which data do we share?

We do not share or sell personally identifiable information (such as name, email) directly with other companies for marketing purposes. We do share Personal Information with vendors (data-processors) who are performing services for Relive, such as the servers for our email communications who are provided access to user's email address for purposes of sending emails from us. Your personal information may be processed outside the EU. We have GDPR compliant Data Processing Addendums in place with our data-processors. Personal data stored at data-processors is removed according to our data retention policy which is described below.

We also utilize external services to help us improve the Relive Website and service. For example, we currently use Google Analytics (traffic analysis), and Wufoo (contact forms). These parties may also use cookies and tracking technologies. Feel free to check out their own Privacy Policies to find out more about how they work.

In the event we undergo a business transaction such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of our assets, your Personal Information may be among the assets transferred. You acknowledge and consent that such transfers may occur and are permitted by this Privacy Policy, and that any acquirer of our assets may continue to process your Personal Information as set forth in this Privacy Policy.

We might also share personal information you have provided to us without your consent, in case we believe:

  * doing so is appropriate to carry out your own request;
  * it's needed to detect, prevent or address fraud, security or technical issues;
  * it's needed to otherwise protect our property, legal rights, or that of others.

#### Privacy Zone

Some third party applications allow you to create a ‘privacy zone’, which will hide your exact location within this zone. Please note that not all third party applications accurately share this information with us, but rather give us the unfiltered data. If you see your route within your privacy zone you must contact your third party service provider to stop sharing locations within your privacy zone.

#### Public link

Please note that the URL of your video leads to our Website or to the Application. This link is publicly accessible.

### How do we protect your personal data?

#### Data protection

We are doing everything possible to protect your personal data from loss, destruction, usage, alterations or distribution by unauthorised persons. Together with our Data Protection Officer, we have a continuous focus on safety and transparency regarding processing of personal data

#### Data retention

We store data as long as it is necessary to provide our service. We delete all your personal information when your account has been inactive for 48 months or when your account is deleted.

#### Backups

We backup data regularly to ensure we can provide a reliable service. We cannot ensure the deletion of your personal data from these backups. In the event that we need to recover a backup, all personal data that is restored with that action will be deleted according to our data retention policy as soon as possible.

#### Third party data

You can always disconnect third party accounts (like Strava or Garmin), upon which we will stop processing data of future activities. Data provided by these third parties while connected is stored and processed similarly to any other Relive data; to completely remove this data see “How can I see, modify, or delete my personal data?” below.

### How can I see, modify, or delete my personal data?

You can see and change part of your data, preferences and notification settings by logging in to your account. If you want to revoke your consent regarding activity, user and usage data processing as described in ‘Why we process personal data’ this means we can no longer provide our service. Therefore you can revoke this consent by deleting your account. If you want to view, export or delete all your personal data, please send an e-mail to dpo@relive.cc, we will act upon your request within 30 days.

#### Photos and Videos

Please note that when you delete your account or ask us to delete your personal data, we delete all your personal data we have stored on our servers. We cannot delete the information you publicly shared, such as a video you shared on Facebook or Instagram or local copies of a video you or people who you shared your video with might have. When you choose to use Relive Together, you allow other Relive Together users to add your photos and route to their videos. We can not remove your data from these videos.

### Cookies

We use cookies to improve your experience on our website. A cookie is a tiny piece of information that will be saved to your computer when you visit our website. Cookies make it possible for our website to recognize you when you return to us. Next to that, because of cookies our website is quicker and safer. Cookies also make it easier for us to spot errors on our website. If you want to disable cookies, you can change the settings of your browser. But please note: you will not have the best experience that our website has to offer.

### Outgoing links

This website and the Application may contain links to other websites. We are not responsible for the content or (lack of) privacy protection of those websites. Therefore, we advise you to always read the privacy statements of the linked websites.

### Alterations of the Privacy Policy

We may update this privacy policy, from time to time. If we alter this policy profoundly, we will notify you by e-mail and we will mention it on the Website.

### Questions?

If you have any questions, you can contact us on: team@relive.cc

Relive B.V.  
E: team@relive.cc  

Number Chamber of Commerce: 67325718  
VAT-number: NL856932917B01

If you have specific questions regarding your personal data, you can contact our Data Protection Officer at dpo@relive.cc.
